# Jack Kershaw

🗣 Wembley, London 🛮 🗷 jackkershaw@protonmail.com 📞 07787 075097 🔗 jackkershaw.net

## **Personal Profile**

I am a Junior Developer with business credentials, having previously run my own graphic design studio. While I still count graphic design as a skill, my passion for IT and desire to solve problems has led me to explore the field of software development.

Along with past experience in digital design software and a range of CMS platforms, I have spent the past year and a half teaching myself the fundamentals of development, including participation in a twelve-week self-funded bootcamp.

I am excited to move into a career as a developer and gain more skills and experience in this field and grow as an IT professional.

# **Education**

Software Development Bootcamp, Just IT Training Ltd

2023 - 2024

Twelve-week intensive bootcamp

**University College London (UCL)** 

2016 - 2020

BA Hons (Greek with Latin)

**Royal Grammar School Guildford** 

2010 - 2016

A-Levels: Latin A, Ancient Greek A, Maths B

GCSEs: 6 A\*s, 3 As

## **Skills**

Frontend: React, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS

Backend: Python and MySQL

Other: Git, Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator, Microsoft Office Suite, Final Cut Pro, CMS (Squarespace, Wix and

Blocs)

# **Projects**

# **London Brutalist Map**

github.com/jones58/brutalist-map

- A map for discovering London's Brutalist buildings.
- · Built using Mapbox API, HTML, CSS and Javascript.

#### **Personal Portfolio**

- github.com/jones58/portfolio-2024
  - A personal portfolio site to show my projects and design work.
  - Built using Vite, React and Tailwind CSS.

## **Daily Challenges**

- github.com/jones58/daily-challenges
  - · Website to link to all the Wordle-adjacent games.
  - Achieved 100 Lighthouse Score across all categories.
  - Built using HTML, CSS and Javascript.

# **Experience**

## **Co-Founder and Graphic Designer**

2019 - 2023

Tapir Studio Limited

- Graphic design focusing on art direction and computer-based design of posters, stickers and social media branding.
- Printed and distributed around 170,000 posters and stickers in the UK and internationally.
- Enterprise management: registering at Companies' House, setting employment terms, distributing work, online sales and liaising with accountants and other outside parties
- Client-facing role: acquiring customers, negotiating terms and providing client service.
- Clients included Oxford University, the TUC, Autonomy, Fête de l'Humanité, UCU, Fossil Free London, Living Rent, London Renters' Union, among many others.
- In August 2022, subject of a full-page feature in the Observer.

Video Editor 2016 - 2022

Freelance

- Created social media videos for the Labour Party, Momentum, The World Transformed, Just Treatment (NHS campaign) and Palestine Solidarity Campaign.
- Effective time management of projects and solving problems with clients.

Sales Associate 2015 - 2016

Cotswold Outdoor, Guildford

- I worked in a team of sales assistants, offering help and advice to members of the public.
- I thrived in a busy environment, serving over fifty customers a day and developing my interpersonal and teamwork skills.

#### **Interests**

- Cycling: Gravel and touring.
- Maintaining a working home server with Linux and Docker for containerised application deployment.
- · Typography

## References

Available upon request